applymagicsauce.com 2018-06-16

# Apply Magic Sauce - Prediction API - Privacy and Cookie Policy

This website is operated by the University of Cambridge Psychometrics Centre, Judge Business School, Trumpington Street, Cambridge, United Kingdom CB2 1AG. This document explains what happens to any personal data that you provide to us, or that we collect from you whilst you visit our site and how we use cookies on this website.

We may update this Policy from time to time. Please review its terms regularly. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions. 

## Information That We Collect

We collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our website. This information constitutes standard web server log data, including the following:

  * Internet address of connecting client
  * Time stamp
  * Request made
  * Server's response code and number of bytes returned
  * The "user agent" string identifying the make of client
  * Your browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics 

If you log in to demos and predictions available on our website, then we also collect certain information that is necessary to provide you with feedback. The content of this is determined by what you choose to share, but may include:

  * Your Facebook user ID, as specific to the Apply Magic Sauce application (note: this is not a universal Facebook platform ID). This is stored in hashed form. 
  * LikeIDs of the Pages you like or follow on Facebook
  * Your Facebook status updates, Tweets and other user-generated text data

We do not collect any social media information about you other than what you explicitly consent to share with the Apply Magic Sauce app via the consent dialogue of the relevant third party platform. We also do not store the results of any predictions generated by this website.

If you contact us through the Contact Form on this website, then we will collect and use the information submitted through it, including your email, for the purpose of responding to your enquiry.

You can view and delete all information that we store about you as a result of you logging into the prediction demo on this website using our [My Data @ Apply Magic Sauce Tool](https://mydata.applymagicsauce.com/). 

## Use of Cookies

Cookies provide information regarding the computer used by a visitor. We use cookies on this site to gather information about your computer in order to enhance your experience and enable certain features.

We use self-expiring session cookies for the purpose of maintaining the test session for a given user. We also use them to anonymously match the session with sessions on our other websites, which are: [youronline.life](https://youronline.life/), [discovermyprofile.com](https://discovermyprofile.com/), [concertoplatform.com](http://concertoplatform.com/) and occasionally other domains that explicitly state if cookies are used in their respective user consent policies. Session matching merely tells us whether it was likely to be the same person using multiple websites we manage, without telling us who this person is.

We also use cookies for Google Analytics, Facebook Social Plugins and Twitter Social Plugins.

Google Analytics is a web analytics tool that helps website owners understand how visitors engage with their website. Google Analytics customers can view a variety of reports about how visitors interact with their website so that they can improve it. Like many services, Google Analytics uses first-party cookies to track visitor interactions as in our case, where they are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. We then use the information to compile reports and to help us improve our site. Google Analytics collects information anonymously. It reports website trends without identifying individual visitors. You can opt out of Google Analytics without affecting how you visit our site. For more information on opting out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites you use, visit <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/>. 

Facebook Social Plugins are optional part of the site and one needs to have a Facebook Account to use them. Their usage is a subject to Facebook’s Data Policy.

Twitter Social Plugins are optional part of the site and one needs to have a Twitter Account to use them. Their usage is a subject to Twitter’s Privacy Policy.

You can adjust the settings on your computer to decline any cookies if you wish. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our site. For more information please read the advice at [AboutCookies.org](http://aboutcookies.org/). 

## Use of Your Information

The information you submit to the website may be used for scientific research purposes, as defined in Recital 159 of the GDPR, which includes for example technological development and demonstration, fundamental research and applied research. The information will be stored for as long as it is relevant for these scientific research purposes, which are conducted in the public interest.

If you have previously visited or submitted data to another website maintained by the University of Cambridge Psychometrics Centre, we may match the data you submit to this website with that other data for the purposes of scientific research and to provide you with more accurate and informative feedback. This matching is done on an anonymous basis using a self-expiring session cookie. We cannot and will not ever attempt to personally identify or contact any individual user of this website.

In operating our website it may become necessary to transfer data that we collect from you to locations outside of the European Union for processing and storing. We will take all reasonable steps to ensure that your data remains secure in such an event.

Lastly, we may use the information we collect in order to comply with applicable laws and to provide you with information that you request from us.

## Disclosure of Information

We may share the information collected by this website with other academic researchers (with a formal University affiliation and email) or with registered charities and non-profits, but only in an anonymous format such that the information can never be used to identify you or any other individual user. We will never share your data with any commercial organisations. We may additional be required to disclose information for the purpose of complying with legal obligations.

## Third Party Links

On occasion we may include links to third parties on this website. Where we provide a link it does not mean that we endorse or approve that site’s policy towards privacy. You should review the third party’s privacy policy before sending them any personal data.

## Access to Information

You have the right to view and delete any information that you have submitted to us through this website at any time. We have built a [My Data @ Apply Magic Sauce Tool](https://mydata.applymagicsauce.com/) to allow you to do this more conveniently.

## Contacting Us

This website was developed and is maintained by the University of Cambridge Psychometrics Centre and UK laws apply to this website. Please direct any enquiries regarding this privacy policy to University of Cambridge Psychometrics Centre, Judge Business School, Trumpington Street, Cambridge CB2 1AG or via Contact Us Form.

The data controller for the purposes of this website is JBS Executive Education Limited (“JBSEEL”), a wholly owned subsidiary of the University of Cambridge (company number 5908393). JBSEEL maintains a data protection notification (registration) with the Information Commissioner and is committed to protecting and respecting individuals’ privacy in compliance with data protection legislation.

If you are not happy with the way your information is being handled, or with the response received from us, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the Information Commissioner’s Office at Wycliffe House, Water Lane, Wilmslow, SK9 5AF.

This Privacy Policy was last modified on 26 March 2018
